https://www.applecookies.com/privacy-policy

Intent
This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how Apple Cookie & Chocolate Co. collects and processes the information that you share when you use our website. Before submitting information to our website, please review and understand this Privacy Policy. By using or accessing our website, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. The following will address all information collected and the intended use of such information.
Personal Information
Personal information you share with us during order placement or user registration is kept confidential. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order or request. Contact information including addresses, email and phone numbers will never be sold to or shared with outside parties. All users who register or place an order will be automatically entered into our marketing campaign, but can opt out at any time by emailing customerservice@applecookies.com or calling 412-825-3550.
Use of Personal Information
Information you share will only be used for the following:
Order Fulfillment
Send Information About Orders
Process and Collect Payments
Provide Promotional Marketing Materials
Cookies
“Cookies” are small text files created by a website that are stored in your computer browser either temporarily or permanently. They are used to recognize and keep track of your preferences to enhance your shopping and browsing experience. Cookies do not contain any information that personally identify you. We use cookies to provide ads based on users’ past visits to our website. You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings (http://www.google.com/settings/ads).
Use of Google Analytics
Apple Cookie & Chocolate Co. uses Google Analytics to collect data and track website performance. Google Analytics uses “cookies” to collect data. This data does not identify you personally. Any information provided to Apple Cookie & Chocolate Co. about your personal identity is kept confidential and not shared in any way with Google or other parties.
Third Party Links
We may provide links to third party websites. We do not own or control these websites and encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies on these sites as well.
Security
Our customers data security is very important to us. Though any transmission of personal data is at your own risk, to ensure correct use of information the appropriate physical, electronic and administrative procedures are in place to safeguard information collected online.
Changes to Privacy Policy
Apple Cookie & Chocolate Co. may change their Privacy Policy in the future. If changes are made, they will be posted here. We advise users to check our Privacy Policy from time to time in to be up to date on any changes.
Contact Us
For any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy please call us at 412-825-3550 or email customerservice@applecookies.com.
